## Paulo Leonardo Benatto

London, UK benatto@gmail.com Phone: 07405110040 Post Code: SW16 2BU

Summary

Bachelor in computer science having expertise in software development, good professional relationship and focused at work. With 6 years of professional experience in software development using basically, C/C++, I am now looking for new challenges and opportunities that allow me to learn new technologies and work with new people.

Education

Universidade Estadual do Oeste do Parana (UNIOESTE), BS in Computer Science, December 2007.

Experience

DBA

Dec 2013 - Feb 2014

System Analyst

Main Tecnologies: Linux, Python, Raspberry PI and C;

I attended of the project to develop a system of vehicle count on Brazilian highways, basically my task was read files with a lot of records and parse all information, store in memory and report this information in a human readable. This project was developed using language C ANSI and Linux platform. The second project that I attended was developing a parking meter system using python language and Raspberry PI. My main task was do inter-process communication using DBus.

SEC+ Dec 2012 - Dec 2013

 $System\ Analyst$ 

Main Tecnologies: Linux, Python, Django Framework, JavaScript and C;

Back-end development of web system for intelligent monitoring and management of natural disasters using Python and the Django framework. Front-end with Javascript (JQuery, Bootstrap, Google Maps API), JSON, HTML5, CSS. Modeling and use of object-relational database and geographic objects with PostgreSQL/PostGIS.

## Digitro Technology - NDS

Jan 2012 - Dec 2012

System analyst

Main Tecnologies: Linux, C ANSI, shellscript, protocols: HTTP, SIP, UDP, TCP;

I worked during one year with great team focused in lawful interception. The most of my time I was working with C language, GCC compiler and Linux platform. Basicly my work was create "parses"(programs) to analyze the content of network packets, extract all information to store on databases.

To ease the work we used the libpcap project. libpcap is a system-independent interface for user-level packet capture. libpcap provides a portable framework for low-level network monitoring. Applications include network statistics collection, security monitoring, network debugging, etc.

To create tests on the project we used the CUnit API and to build and execute them, we created a jenkins environment.

I worked a little bit with java, our team was big, and I would like to learn another world. =)

Digitro Technology - STE

Set 2008 - Dec 2011

System analyst

Main Tecnologies: Linux, VoIP, C/C++, shellscript, protocols: UDP, TCP, SIP;

I worked a little bit with embedded systems developing an IP Phone. I was responsible to cross-compile EFL (Enlightenment Foundation Libraries) and develop the IP Phone interface. I had to work with a design team, this was awesome.

I worked in a team to develop a softphone (program for making telephone calls over the Internet) using C/C++ language and Windows platform. I studied a lot SIP, UDP, TCP and others protocols.

In some moments I worked with shell, lua and python (scripting). I had to administer Linux systems, Asterisk, OpenSER, Kamailio and others.

Virtual Office

Jan 2008 - Aug 2008

 $Developer\ Jr$ 

Main Tecnologies: Linux, VoIP, SIP, Asterisk and Latex;

This was my first formal job and I learned a lot with great professionals. Here I worked with Asterisk and Linux administration. We created an asterisk advanced course (using latex).

I worked a little bit with PHP and MySQL, to customize the web page administration of our product.

Skills Base

Operating System: Linux (Debian, Ubuntu, CentOS and others), Windows NT/XP/Vista/7 and OSX;

Network Protocols: IP, TCP, UDP, HTTP, SIP, FTP, SMTP, SNMP, e outros;

Progamming Languages: C, Python, JavaScript, plus some experience with lua / Java / Ruby / PHP / HTML;

Virtualization: VirtualBox, VMWare, plus some experience with Xen;

Languages: Fluent in Portuguese, Intermediate in English and Spanish;

## Open Source Projects

In my spare time I develop some open source projects (https://github.com/patito/).

- libpenetra: The libpenetra was created with the goal of studying the windows binary format known as Portable Executable (PE). With libpenetra you can access all information about PE binaries. (https://github.com/patito/libpenetra)
- libmalelf: The libmalelf is an evil library that SHOULD be used for good! It was developed with the intent to assist in the process of infecting binaries and provide a safe way to analyze malwares. (https://github.com/SecPlus/libmalelf)
- malelf: Malelf is a tool that uses libmalelf to dissect and infect ELF binary. (https://github.com/SecPlus/malelf)

More Info

- Linkedin: http://www.linkedin.com/in/benatto
- **Github**: https://github.com/patito